[{"answer": "Really", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "\"Off the wago", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yeah. He's been off the wagon for two years", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I think it's off the wagon", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "\"Off the wago", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I think it's", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I though I'd never find it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No. Today's", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Oh, uh, I think maybe my friend picked up yours", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I didn't know you meant", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " Oh, here. This is why", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "See this red dot", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "It's hard to say", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Well I can see it", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well what do you want me to do? Not look at it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "It's hard to pretend because I know where it is", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "It's hard to pretend because I know where it is", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You want me to take an overview", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "He's acting very strangely. I think he started drinking again", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "No. I can't smell it", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well if you can't smell it then he hasn't been drinking", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Yes you do", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Hey what's that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Christmas present? For who", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " Uh, I don't know. Uh, I don't know", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Ahem. Say that again", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Do I see it... or don't I? That's the question. my friend goes to the counter and pours some scotch. He drinks it. He comes back groggy", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "So she starts vaccuming, back and forth, back and forth, her hips swivelling, her breasts, uh...", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Convulsing", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You knew he was an alcoholic. Why'd you put the drink down at all", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I'm not saying anything", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "What are you saying", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You're saying something", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I'm not saying anything", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "What could I be saying", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You're saying something", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Well you're not saying nothing you must be saying something", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "What could I be saying", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "If I was saying something I would have said it", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Well why don't you say it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "What did you say", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Hey, let me ask you something something. Did my friend buy that sweater knowing the red dot was on it because it was cheaper?  Ooookay, you just gave me the answer", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Yes you did, yes you did. I saw your expression", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I'm not swearing. I don't want to swear", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Do you swear", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Oh you told her didn't you", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Hey my friend, did you buy that sweater knowing that red dot was on it because you could get it at a discount", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "You did didn't you", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "You never had sex in the office before", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Alright so you made out with someone", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Well that's not sex", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Red-Dot.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Kissing is not sex", "qsentId": 54}]